• dguard

🏏 @_extj

in alexander-serditov

@inkata_knight

sav.serditov

av.serditov@gmail.com



Alexander Serditov

Full Stack Developer (Django, Yii, Node, Ruby)

During my development experience I participated 20+ projects. The primary focus includes interactions between people and devices. There are different directions: marketing and social activities, IoT, educational projects, neuromarketing and user behaviour, advertisement campaigns, VoIP platform.

My jorney at Web Development started at 2007 year. Step by step I grow from junior developer with common knowledge into lead developer with skills in architecture prototyping. First prio skills includes communication with people, concept, design, implementation.

I prefer work at freelance cause it gives opportunities to improve skills in sport, cybersport, travel into cities, countries where I may reach people

There exists a company Digitally Constructed (DC). I created projects that allow improve skills in sport and cybersport, meet with other people, communicate with people, have a community. Technologies provides an opportunity to manage nance fonds, deliver a payment transaction.

Primary Skills

There are highly desired skills. These skills are widely used across participated projects

Django

- Yii framework
- Node.js (Express.js)
- Docker, Docker Compose
- AWS EC2, AWS EB
- Babel, Gulp, Webpack
- CSS, SASS, LESS, CSS3
- Html, Html5
- RabbitMQ
- Celery
- Supervisor
- Nginx
- Angular 1+, Angular 2+
- NativeScript, TypeScript

Secondary Skills

During my programming experience I used next skills to reach best results alongside main development activity. I may use these skills for position at junior level. There are especially interesting products from Amazon and Open Source Community

- Ruby On Rails
- Android SDK
- SMTP
- Postgres, DynamoDB
- Unix, Bash

Employment History

Latest projects are done for Digitally Constructed (DC).

Freelance Web Developer

Sep 2009 - Present

Why working as Freelance Web Developer very perspective for me?

- It gives an opportunity to manage time frames during working and
- resting
- It provides an opportunity to travel across countries and cities
- It provides an opportunity to keep and improve skills using concrete
- training schedule
- It provides an opportunity to work directly with leaders of IT industry as
- well as startups companies

React and Node Developer | XDefi Technologies Ltd Mar 2021 - May 2021

The solution for ethereum blockchain (as well for ethereum nft, bitcoin, litecoin, binance, binance smart chain) to take a look transaction list for different cryptocurrencies, provides possibility to be easy scalable (cares about rpm for concrete cryptocurrency channel). Provides option to spawn new instances based on rpm on amazon elastic beanstalk and amazon ec2

Client (Chrome, Firefox): React

API (ethereum, ethereum nft and other): Node, Nest

Deployer: Node **Proxy**: Nginx

RPM bandwidth provider: Node, Nest

Load Testing: Cypress, Bash Request Testing (via Postman) Amazon Instances: Amazon EC2 Amazon Storage: Amazon S3

Amazon Deployer Solution: Amazon ElasticBeanstalk, Amazon Fargate,

Amazon ECS

React Native Developer | Trinity

Dec 2020 - Mar 2021

Good application for retail (android, ios), it provides an opportinity for product owner to take a look available items inside different points of sale, get details about revenue, roi. Interface is available on ios and android. I was involved into development both frontend and backend sides. React Native for android and ios, React for frontend, Kafka as message broker, Node and Nest on backend side.

Device (Android, IOS): React Native **Client (Chrome, Firefox):** React

Data Pipeline: kafka

Image Storage (aka Amazon S3): Node

Authentication: Auth0

Broker Availability Monitor: React Compute Instances: Yandex Cloud

Developer | Apivio Clive

Dec 2016 - Apr 2017

The product was created for the company to manage rmware and software on connected devices in VoIP industry. I had a position of developer, did tasks using RabbitMQ, Celery, Django. RabbitMQ as well as bash very good for ditributed system handling management devices. There were very cool interaction within teammmates and chief artchitect

Firmware Provider (via API): Django Client (Chrome, Firefox): Django Request Testing (via Postman)

Unit Testing: unittest

Lead Developer | Results On Air Sep 2015 - April 2016

The Amazon Web Services has an accelerator #500Strong. I was luckly to join into one of the projects on position of lead developer. We did product that provides an opportunity to take ROI, revenue on data from TV campaigns and provide time options for this advertisement for required segment of people that increases primary metrics. Worked with mates from GB, stack includes node, redshift, angular 1+

Client (Chrome, Firefox): Angular 1.5, RaphaelJS, Highcharts

Data Warehouse (TV Campaign): Amazon Redshift

Client's Data Warehouse: DynamoDb

Unit Testing: Mocha, Sinon

API: Node, Express

Amazon Instances: Amazon EC2
Amazon Storage: Amazon S3

Amazon Deployer Solution: Amazon ElasticBeanstalk

Developer | Pathful

Dec 2014 - Apr 2015

Another great project for marketing. Marketing campaign has goals for user, the solution allows construct a heatmap of user actions on website across used devices and website pages. The makreting campaign's owner has an option to reach goals and have a state of already published goals. We used django and client side javascript to have mentioned things done

Client (Chrome, Firefox): JavaScript

Backend: SQLAlchemy, Flask **Unit Testing**: unittest, unittest2 **Request Testing**: postman

Developer | RSVPU

Sep 2012 - Apr 2014

Educational system for Russian State Pedagogical University. My role as developer was simple. Stack includes Yii

Client (Chrome, Firefox): Yii

Backend: Yii

Request Testing: Yii Debugger

Lead Developer | Dashify

Sep 2012 - Aug 2014

The solution for social networks to take metrics in one place. We have a set of mockups in really high quality, stack includes Yii, bash, search engine

Client (Chrome, Firefox): Yii

Backend: Yii

Request Testing: Yii Debugger

Education

Computer Science | Russian State Vocational Pedagogical University

Sep 2010 - May 2015

Secondary School

Sep 2005 - May 2010